Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- E
  - Engler, Mitchell L., undated (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Eplan, Ray, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Epstein, Harry, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Epstein, Helen, undated (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Erb, John W., undated (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Erdman, Jean, undated (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Erdman, John F., undated (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Ericson, Louis, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Erim, Kenan T., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Ernst, Fred, undated (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Ertegun, Ahmet, undated (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Ervin, Ellen, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Ervin, Samuel, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Erwin, Frank Alexander, undated (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Escaladas, Emilio, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Eskridge, Bill, circa 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Esquirol, John H., undated (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Estreicher, Samuel, 1984, 1989, circa 1990s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Estrin, Harvey, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Etgen, William C., 1960 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Ettinger, Richard P., 1961, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Ettinger, Virgil P., 1952 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ettinghausen, Richard, 1967, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Eugeberg, Al, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Eurythmics, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Eustace, James S., 1960, 1979, 1983, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Evans, Eli N., undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Evans, Jane, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Evans, John D., undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Evans, Lester, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Melvin J., undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Everts, Margot, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Ewing, Dr. James, undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Ewing, Dr. Parmer L., undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Exum, James, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
- F
  - Faber, Benjamin S. "Bunny", 1930 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Fabian, Simon, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Fabricant, Solomon, 1966, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Fabrikant, William, circa 1934 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Fackenthal, Frank D., 1948 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Fackler, Clarence, undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Fafunwa, Dr. A. Babs, undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Fagg, John E., undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Fairchild, H.P., undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Fairfield, Kent, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Fales, Decoursey, 1942, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Fales, Haliburton, undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Falk, Irving, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Falk, Minna R., 1956 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Falknor, undated (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Falnes, Oscar, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Fambro, Carlton, undated (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Farber, Barry, undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Farber, Saul, 1965, 1975, 1983, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Fargotson, Florence, undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Farina, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Farkas, George, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Farkas, Joe, undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Farkas, Ruth, 1965, 1980, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Farma, William J., undated (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Farrell, Mary, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Farrington-Brathwaite, Anita, undated (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Fass, Rita D., undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Fauenbach, Ken, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Fayerweather, John, 1962, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Feddersen, Jack R., 1972 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Feder, Richard, undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Federman, Barry, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Federman, Hyman L., undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Feeney, Floyd F., undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Feibish, Bernard, circa 1937 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Feil, Henry, circa 1938 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Fein, Harry D., 1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Feinsot, Aaron, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Feinstein, Valerie, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Feitlane, Carol, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Felder, Myrna, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Feldman, Eric, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Feldman, Noah, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Feldman, Orin, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Feldman, Dr. Samuel, 1972, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Feldman, Sandra, undated (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Felicia, Gladys, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Felton, Duane, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Felzenberg, Leonard J., undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Fendala, C., undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Fennelly, Brian, undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Fenner, undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Fenster, Deborah, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Ferejohn, John, undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Fergus, Jean and Colin, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Ferguson, Bob, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Ferguson, Gerard, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Ferguson, James T., undated (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - Ferguson, M. Carr, 1962, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Ferguson, Wallace K., 1953 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Ferguson, Walter F.C., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Ferkauf, Sid, undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Fernwald, Henry B., undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Fernandez, undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Fernandez, Oscar, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Fernandez, Raquel, undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Fernicola, Tony, undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Ferral, Victor E., undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Ferrara, Angelo, 1952, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Ferrer, Fernando J., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Ferrera, Laurence, undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Ferrero, Henry J., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Ferri, Antonio, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Ferris, Dr. Albert Warren, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Ferris, Isaac, 1933, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Ferris, Richard B., 1943 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Ferte, B., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Fertig, Lawrence, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Festinger, Trude, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Feugchun, Jin, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Fichandler, Zelda, undated (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Ficken, Frederick, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Fiedler, Leslie, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Field, David Dudley, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Field, Storm, undated (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Fields, Dorothy, undated (Box 119, Folder 38)
  - Fields, Morey R., 1961 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Fields, Ted, undated (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Fields, Walter L., 1990 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Fijnaut, Cyrille, undated (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Filardi, Al, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Findley, Father, undated (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Fine, Toni, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Finebaum, Murray, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Fink, undated (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Fink, Barbara, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Finke, Howard, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Finkelstein, Jerry, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Finkler, Steven, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Finlay, George, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Finley, Mary A., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Finn, Al, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Finn, Vincent, circa 1941 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Finner, Stephen, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Finney, David, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Fiore, Albert, circa 1945 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Fiore, Fred W., undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - First, Harry, 1980-1990 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Firstenberg, Meyer, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Fisch, Gene, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Fischer, Alfred, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Fischer, David, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Fischer, Avery, 1975-1994 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Fischer, Lester, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Fischer, Robert, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Fish, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Fishbein, Louis, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Fisher, E.D., undated (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Fisher, John H., 1963 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Fisher, Richard, undated (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Fishman, James, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Fishman, Sidney, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Fitzgerald, Garret, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, undated (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Fitzgerald, Le Roy, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Fitzwilliams, Barbara, undated (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Flack, John B., undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Flamm, Donald, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Flanagan, Eugene J.T., 1983 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Flanders, Ralph B., undated (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Flanz, Gilbert H., 1982 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Flaubert, Gustave, undated (Box 119, Folder 39)
  - Flavio, Steven T., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Flaxman, Seymour, undated (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Fleck, Henrietta, 1961-1973 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Fleischhauer, Carl August, undated (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Fleishman, Raymond, undated (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Fleming, Claire, undated (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Fleming, Dan, undated (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Fleming, Robert S., 1958 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Flemming, Arthur S., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Flint, Austin III, undated (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Flom, Joseph H., 1992
    - Photographs (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 40)
  - Florio, Jim, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Florio, Joseph, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Florio, Steven T., undated (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Floyd, Barry, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Floydysh, undated (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Flynn, James A. Jr., 1985 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Foch, Marshal Ferdinand, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Fodor, Iris, undated (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Foley, Esther V., undated (Box 119, Folder 41)
  - Foley, James A., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Foley, Richard, undated (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Foley, Tom, undated (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Follet, Beryl M., undated (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Foltz, Dave B., undated (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Fontaine, A.P., 1961, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Foot, Hugh Mackintosh, 1965, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Flores, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ford, Eileen, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1978, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Ford, Jack, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Ford, Kristina, circa 2006 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Fordyce, John A., undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Foreman, Matt, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Foreman, Richard (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Forer, Irwin, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Forester, John J., 1957, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Forgotson, Florence, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Forman, Donald, undated
    - Photographs (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 42)
  - Forman, MiloÅ¡, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Forrest, Charles D., undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Forrester, Robert H., undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Fortiages, Nicholas, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Foskett, Eben, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Fosteu, Jack, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Foster, Henry, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Foster, Jodie, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Foster, Kenneth, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Foster, Rose Marie Perez, undated
    - Photographs (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 43)
  - Fottrell, John Francis, circa 1940 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Foucault, Michel, undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Fowkes, Robert, 1952, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Fowler, Libby, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Fox, Donald T., 1983 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Fox, Eleanor, 1985-1990
    - Photographs (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 44)
  - Fox, Marcia, 1976, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Foxhall, Lorraine, undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Foxman, Abe, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Foxx, Anthony, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Foye, Arthur B., 1956 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Franc, Helen, undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Francesco, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Franck, Thomas, 1963-1997 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - François, Aderson, undated (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Frank, Beatrice, 1983-1995 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Frank, George, undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Frank, Gloria, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Frank, Harry B., 1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Frank, Manuel, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Frank, Sally, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Frank, Thomas, 1963, 1980 (Box 119, Folder 45)
  - Frankel, L.R., undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Franklin, Ed, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Franz, Albert, circa 1941 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Fraser-Abder, Pamela, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Frazor, Terence, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Freccero, John, 1994
    - Photographs (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 46)
  - Frederick, Robert F., 1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Freedberg, Dr. Irwin, undated (Box 119, Folder 47)
  - Freedman, Eric, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Freedman, Michael, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Freedman, Richard, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Freedman, Sharon, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Freeh, Louis J., undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Freeman, Douglas, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Freeman, Harry J., 1942 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Freeman, Roland G., undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Fregosi, Robert, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Freidrichs, Kurt O., 1965 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Freimann, John, 1954-1958 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Freitag, Steve, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Frelinghuysen, Theodore, undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - French, Charlie, undated (Box 119, Folder 48)
  - French, F.C., undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - French, Maryanna Douglas, undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - French, Thomas Clayton, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Frenkeil, François N., 1963 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Freudenthal, Dr. Peter, 1954 (Box 119, Folder 49)
  - Frey, Alan, undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Frey, Walter G. Jr., undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Fribourg, Paul J., undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Fried, Charles, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Friedan, Betty, undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Friedlander, Eva, undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Friedlander, Judith, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Friedlander, Miriam, undated (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Friedlander, Percy, circa 1920 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Friedman, Dr. Alvin, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Friedman, Barry, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Friedman, Jerome, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Friedman, Joel, undated (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Friedman, Leslie, undated (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Friedman, Marc, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Friedman, Mark, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Friedman, Paul, undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Friedman, Sharon, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Friedman, Sharon, undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Friedrich, Anton A., undated (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Friedrichs, Kurt, undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Friedson, Eliot, undated (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Friel, Brian, undated (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Friend, James P., 1967 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Friendly, Fred, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Frischer, Ruth, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Fritz, Charles A., 1942 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Fritz, John, undated (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Froatz, Frances, undated (Box 119, Folder 50)
  - Frohnmayer, John E., undated (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Frolin, Dennis, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Frommer, Robert, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Frontera, Jim, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Frost, Everett, undated (Box 119, Folder 51)
  - Fruehling, Don, undated (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Fruman, Thomas, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Frusciano, Thomas J., undated (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Frydenborg, Clarence Martin, circa 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Fryer, Douglas, 1923, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Frypanis, undated (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Fuchs, Beverly, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Fuchs, Michael, undated (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Fuchs, Sol, circa 1934 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Fuchsberg, Jacob, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Fuentes, Carlos, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Fuersich, Bernie, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Fujikura, Koichiro, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Fulbright, J. William, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Fuller, Sam, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Fulmer, Terry, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Fulshaw, Donald, circa 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Fung, Margaret, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Funk, Michael Sean, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Funston, George Keith, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Furgang, Philip, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Furiel, Ralph, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Furmaski, Phil, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Fusco, John, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Fusfeld, Herbert I., undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
- G
  - Gabor, Stanley, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Gabriel, Mabel McAfee, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Gabriel, Martha, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Gabrielsen, Milton, undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Gades, Henry Lewis, undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Gagnon, Trip, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Gaidzis, Nap, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Gainsbrugh, Martin R., undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Gal, Lenny, undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Galbraith, Evan, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Galbraith, J.K., 1983 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Galeano, Cataldo Aldo, circa 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Gallatin, Albert, undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Gallatin, Albert E., circa 1940 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Gallatin, Albert H., 1882 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Gallaudet, Thomas, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Galliard, Clem, 1961, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Gallob, Mitch, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Galloway, Lee, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Gallup, George H., 1936 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Galo, William, undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Galowitz, Paula, 1993
    - Photographs (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 52)
  - Galvin, Robert, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Galway, James, undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Gambell, James, undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Gammage, Amory, undated (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Ganakas, Greg, undated (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Gander, Dionne, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Gandhi, Indira, undated (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Gandley, Joseph Francis, circa 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Gans, David, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Gans, Dr. Paul, undated (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Ganz, Paul, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Garabedian, Paul, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Garavoy, Marvin, undated (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Garbus, Martin, undated (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Garcia, David, undated (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Garcia, Luis, undated (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Gardner, John, undated (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Gardner, Robert, undated (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Garelli, Jacques, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Garibaldi, Antoine, undated (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Garland, David, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Garmany, J.J., undated (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Garner, James, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Garniez, Bernard, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Garo, undated (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Garreau, Irma, undated (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Garretson, Albert H., undated (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Garrett, James F., undated (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Garrison, Jim, undated (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Garth, David, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Gartner, Michael G., 1988 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Garud, Raghu, undated (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Garvin, Edwin L., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 69, Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Gary, Elbert E., undated (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Gasparitsch, Edward, undated (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Gately, Dermot, undated (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, undated (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Gaurilova, Maria, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Gauss, Christian, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Gavison, Ruth, undated (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Gaylor, Mike, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Gaylor, Peter, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Gedder, Robert, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Geddes, Robert, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Geffen, Perry, circa 1934-1935 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Geffner, William, circa 1936-1937 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Gehm, Rudolph, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Geismar, Arthur B., 1935 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Geistfeld, Mark, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Gelb, Arthur, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Gelb, Lawrence, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Gelder, Irving L., undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Geldmacher, Robert C., 1960 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Gellman, Peter I., 1963 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Geneen, Harold S., 1956, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Geneva, Jayne, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gendzhelder, Henry, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Genns, Duncan M., undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Gentile, Carolyn, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Gentile, Vincent E., undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Gentul, Jack, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - George, Allan C., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - George, J.K., undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - George, Zelma Watson, undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Geracioti, Lawrence J., 1964-1968, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Gerard, George, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Gerdes, John, undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Gerdes, Victor, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Gerlach, Kristin, undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Germain, Bree, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Germans, Jacques, undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Gerrard, undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Gersh, Irwin Edward, circa 1940 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Gershon, Alyssa L., undated (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Gershoy, Leo, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Gershwin, Ira, undated (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Gerstenberg, Charles W., 1943 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Gerster, John, undated (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Gerstman, Louis, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Gertler, Mark, undated (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Gescher, Mark, 1966, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Gessner, Robert, 1941, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Gettler, Jiseoh D., 1971 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Gerry, Ann, 1985, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Getty, Gordon, undated (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Geururz, Zeu, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Gewirtzman, Doni, undated (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Ghee, Albert, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 49, Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Ghezzo, Dino, undated (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Ghosh, Avijit, undated (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Giannini, Mario C., undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Giannoulos, Stacy, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Giarda, Raffaela, undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Gibbs, Jenny, undated (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Gibson, Kenneth, undated (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Gibson, Walker, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Gibson, William M., 1964 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Giddings, Horace A., 1969 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Giddon, Donald B., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Giger, Marcel, undated (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Gilbert, Creighton, undated (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Gilbert, John, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Gilbert, Ralph W., undated (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Gilchrist, Kimberly, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Giles, H. Henry, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Gill, Patricia, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 67)
  - Gillen, Karen, circa 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 68)
  - Gillers, Stephen, undated (Box 41, Folder 69)
  - Gillespie, Bill, undated (Box 41, Folder 70)
  - Gillespie, Karen, 1957, 1961, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Gillet, William, 1903 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Gillette, Clayton, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Gillette, E.M., circa 1938-1939 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Gilliam, Terry, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gilligan, Carol, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Gilligan, Frank, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gilligan, John, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gilligan, Michael, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Gilloon, James V. Jr., 1952, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Gillpatric, Roswell, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Gilmour, Lloyd S., 1958 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Gilot, Francoise, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Gilsenan, Michael, undated (Box 119, Folder 53)
  - Gingold, Jeff, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Ginsberg, Faye, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, undated
    - Photographs (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Negatives (Box 119, Folder 54)
  - Girard, Richard A., 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Gitlow, Abraham, 1965-1985 (Box 42, Folder 19-20)
  - Gittleson, Steven, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1985-1998 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Giuliano, Samuel, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Glade, Frederic, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Gladwin, Thomas, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 25)